Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 5583/6
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- AT&T (American Telephone and Telegraph), 1950-1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bell Telephone Magazine, 1950-1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    Author: AT&T (American Telephone and Telegraph)
    Notes: v.29:no.2 (1950:Summer)-v.33:no.3 (1954:Autumn)
- Penn Central Railroad, 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Mutual Magazine, 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    Author: Penn Central Railroad
    Notes: v.57 (1971)-v.58 (1973)
- Penn Central Railroad, 1973-1975 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Mutual Magazine, 1973-1975 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.59 (1973)-v.60 (1975)
- Conference for Progressive Labor Action, 1930-1931 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Age, 1930-1931 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Author: Conference for Progressive Labor Action
    Notes: v.19 (1930)-v.20 (1931)
- Conference for Progressive Labor Action, 1932-1933 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor Age, 1932-1933 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21 (1932)-v.22:no.1 (1933:Feb./Mar.)
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1961-1963 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1961-1963 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1 (1961)-v.3 (1963)
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1964-1966 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1964-1966 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4 (1964)-v.6 (1966)
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1967-1970 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1967-1970 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7 (1967)-v.10 (1970)
- General Motors Corporation, 1972-1975 (Box 83A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Delco-Remy Clan, 1972-1975 (Box 83A, Folder 1)
    Author: Delco-Remy Division
    Notes: v.52:no.1 (1972:Jan. 11) - v.55:no.11 (1975:Dec.). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1960-1961 (Box 83A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Electric Schnectady News, 1960-1961 (Box 83A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.43:no.1 (1960:Jan. 8) - v.44:no.52 (1961:Dec. 29)
- General Electric, 1961-1962 (Box 83A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Electric Erie News, 1961-1962 (Box 83A, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.42:no.1 (1961:Jan. 6) - v.43:no.50 (1962:Dec. 28). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1963-1964 (Box 83B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Electric Erie News, 1963-1964 (Box 83B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.1 (1961:Jan. 4) - v.45:no.50 (1962:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1965-1966 (Box 83B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Electric Erie News, 1965-1966 (Box 83B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1961:Jan. 8) - v.47:no.50 (1962:Dec. 30). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1967-1968 (Box 83B, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Electric Erie News, 1967-1968 (Box 83B, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.48:no.1 (1967:Jan. 6) - v.49:no.49 (1968:Dec. 20). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1969-1970 (Box 83B, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General Electric Erie News, 1969-1970 (Box 83B, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.50:no.1 (1969:Jan. 3) - v.51:no.25 (1970:June 19). Bound volume.
- Lockheed-California Company, 1971-1974 (Box 84A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Lockheed Star, 1971-1974 (Box 84A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.38:no.1 (1971:Jan. 8) - v.41:no.25 (1974:Dec. 19). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1968-1969 (Box 84A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1968-1969 (Box 84A, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.4661 (1968:Jan. 5) - no.4738 (1969:July 4). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1971; Publication (Box 84A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1971; Publication (Box 84A, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.4816 (1971:Jan. 1) - no.4868 (1971:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1969-1970 (Box 84B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1969-1970 (Box 84B, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.4739 (1968:July 11) - no.4815 (1970:Dec. 25). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1972; Publication (Box 84B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1972; Publication (Box 84B, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.4869 (1972:Jan. 7) - no.4920 (1972:Dec. 29). Bound volume.
- Trade Courier Corporation, 1963-1968 (Box 84B, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1963-1968 (Box 84B, Folder 3)
    Author: Trade Courier Corporation
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1963:Mar.) - v.33:no.1 (1968:Jan.)
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.4921 (1973:Jan. 5) - no.4971 (1973:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.4926 (1973:Jan. 5) - no.5022 (1974:Dec. 20). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1975-1976 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1975-1976 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.5023 (1968:Jan. 3) - no.5081 (1976:Feb. 20). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1943-1944 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1943-1944 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1943:Jan.) - v.30:no.12 (1944:Dec.). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1945-1946 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1945-1946 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1945:Jan.) - v.32:no.12 (1946:Dec.). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1947-1949 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1947-1949 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1947:Jan.) - v.35:no.12 (1949:Dec.). Bound volume. Incomplete.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1950-1952 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1950-1952 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.1 (1950:Jan.) - v.38:no.7 (1952:July). Bound volume. Incomplete.
- Labor Publication Society, 1928-1929 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor Age, 1928-1929 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    Author: Labor Publication Society
    Notes: v.17:no.2 (1928:Feb.) - v.18:no.12 (1929:Dec.). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1962-1963 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Electric Schnectady News, 1962-1963 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.45:no.1 (1962:Jan. 5) - v.46:no.52 (1963:Dec. 27)
- General Electric, 1964-1965 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Electric Schnectady News, 1964-1965 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.47:no.1 (1964:Jan. 3) - v.48:no.53 (1965:Dec. 30)
- General Electric, 1966-1967 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Electric Schnectady News, 1966-1967 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.49:no.1 (1966:Jan. 7) - v.50:no.51 (1967:Dec. 22)
- General Electric, 1968-1969 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General Electric Schnectady News, 1968-1969 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.51:no.1 (1968:Jan. 5) - v.52:no.50 (1961:Dec. 26)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1928-1930 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1928-1930 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Author: New Jersey Bell Telephone
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1928:Oct.) - v.3:no.12 (1929:Sep.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1930-1934 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1930-1934 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1928:Oct.) - v.7:no.12 (1934:Sep.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1934-1939 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1934-1939 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1934:Oct.) - v.12:no.11/12 (1939:Aug./Sep.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1939-1943 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1939-1943 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1939:Oct.) - v.16:no.12 (1943:Sep.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1943-1947 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1943-1947 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1943:Oct.) - v.20:no.11/12 (1947:Aug./Sep.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1947-1950 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1947-1950 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1947:Oct.) - v.23:no.12 (1950:Sep.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1950-1953 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1950-1953 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (1950:Oct.) - v.26:no.12 (1953:Sep.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1953-1956 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1953-1956 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.27:no.1 (1953:Oct.) - v.29:no.15 (1956:Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1957-1958 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1957-1958 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.1 (1951:Jan.) - v.31:no.12 (1958:Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1959-1960 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1959-1960 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.1 (1959:Jan.) - v.33:no.12 (1960:Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1961-1962 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1961-1962 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.1 (1961:Jan.) - v.35:no.12 (1962:Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.1 (1963:Jan.) - v.37:no.12 (1964:Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1965-1966 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1965-1966 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.1 (1965:Jan.) - v.39:no.12 (1966:Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1967-1968 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1967-1968 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.40:no.1 (1967:Jan.) - v.41:no.6 (1968:Nov./Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.1 (1969:Jan./Feb.) - v.43:no.6 (1970:Nov./Dec.)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1971-1975 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1971-1975 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.44:no.1 (1971:Jan./Feb.) - v.48:no.4 (1975)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Bell, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.1 (1976) - no.4 (1977)
- Long Island Railroad, 1920-1925 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Personnel Service, 1945-1949 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Author: NRDGA (National Retail Dry Goods Association), Personnel Group
    Notes: May/June, 1945 - Nov./Dec. 1949
  - Item 2: Long Island Railroad Information Bulletin, 1920-1925 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Author: Long Island Railroad
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1920:Sep. 30) - v.3:no.6 (1925:Mar. 16). Bound volume.
- NRDGA (National Retail Dry Goods Association), Personnel Group, 1945-1949 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Personnel Service, 1945-1949 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Long Island Railroad Information Bulletin, 1920-1925 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Long Island Railroad, 1925-1928 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Long Island Railroad Information Bulletin, 1925-1928 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1925:June 3) - v.5:no.7 (1928:Nov./Dec.). Bound volume.
- Long Island Railroad, 1929-1931 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Long Island Railroad Information Bulletin, 1929-1931 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1929:Jan./Feb.) - v.7:no.3 (1931:Nov./Dec.). Bound volume.
- John A. Roebling's Sons Company, 1947-1949 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Roebling Record, 1947-1949 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1947:Aug. 15) - v.2:no.9 (1949:Apr.). Bound volume.
- Labor Research Association, 1936-1939 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Sheet and Metal Notes, 1936-1939 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    Author: Labor Research Association
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1936:Jan.) - v.7:no.12 (1939:Oct.). Bound volume.
- Lever Brothers Company, 1921-1929 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Lever Standard, 1921-1929 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (1921:Jan.) - v.7:no.11 (1929:Apr./May). Bound volume.
- Lever Brothers Company, 1929-1939 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Lever Standard, 1929-1939 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1929:June/July)- v.11:no.12 (1938:Dec./1939:Jan.). Bound volume.
- Lever Brothers Company, 1939-1944 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Lever Standard, 1939-1944 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1939:Feb./Mar.) - v.16:no.10 (1944:Dec.). Bound volume.
- Lever Brothers Company, 1945-1948 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Lever Standard, 1945-1948 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1945:Jan.) - v.20:no.1 (1947:Dec./1948:Jan.). Bound volume.
- Lever Brothers Company, 1951-1954 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Lever Standard, 1951-1954 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (1951:Jan.) - v.26:no.6 (1954:Aug./Sep.). Bound volume.
- The Pullman Company, 1922-1924 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Pullman News, 1922-1924 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    Author: The Pullman Company
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1922:May) - v.2:no.12 (1924:Apr.). Bound volume.
- The Pullman Company, 1924-1927 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Pullman News, 1924-1927 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1924:May) - v.5:no.12 (1927:Apr.). Bound volume.
- The Pullman Company, 1927-1930 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Pullman News, 1927-1930 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1927:May) - v.8:no.12 (1930:Apr.). Bound volume.
- The Pullman Company, 1930-1934 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Pullman News, 1930-1934 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1930:May) - v.12:no.4 (1934:Apr.). Bound volume.
- The Pullman Company, 1934-1943 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Pullman News, 1934-1943 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1934:July) - v.21:no.4 (1943:Apr.). Bound volume.
- The Pullman Company, 1944-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Pullman News, 1944-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.22:no.4 (1944:Apr.) - v.28:no.1 (1949:Oct.). Bound volume.
- The Pullman Company, 1950-1958 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Pullman News, 1950-1958 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.2 (1950:Jan.) - v.36:no.1 (1958:Jan.). Bound volume.
- The Texas Company, 1925-1927 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: the Texaco Star, 1925-1927 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    Author: The Texas Company
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1925:Jan.) - v.14:no.12 (1927:Dec.). Bound volume.
- The Texas Company, 1928; Publication (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: the Texaco Star, 1928; Publication (Box 94, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.1-12 (1928:Jan.-Dec.). Bound volume.
- The Texas Company, 1929-1930 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: the Texaco Star, 1929-1930 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (1929:Jan.) - v.17:no.11 (1930:Dec.). Bound volume.
- The Texas Company, 1931-1940 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: the Texaco Star, 1931-1940 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1931:Jan.) - v.26:no.3 (1940:Asphalt Number). Bound volume.
- The Texas Company, 1940-1948 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: the Texaco Star, 1940-1948 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.1 (1940:Power Industry Number) - v.35:no.1 (1948:Winter). Bound volume.
- The Texas Company, 1949-1959 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: the Texaco Star, 1949-1959 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.3 (1949:Summer) - v.65:no.4 (1958/1959:Winter). Bound volume.